

LANGUAGES

Native Spanish:

English: B2 - Studying C1

ABOUT ME

I am a 20-year-old student, with a great passion for computing, more specifically for the part of AI and neural networks or cybersecurity.

Focused on my studies and profession. Efficient and productive.

Senior Technician in Multiplatform Application Development and future student of artificial intelligence + robotics engineering.

CONTACT

i.martin.desarrollo@gmail.com

+34 659 86 56 17

Madrid, Spain

Portfolio











LUMBRERAS MARTIN

CROSS-PLATFORM DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

Indra | March 2023 - June 2023

Computer Technician Internship King Juan Carlos Hospital | April 2021 - June 2021

EDUCATION

2021 - 2023

CFGS Multiplatform Application Development

CES Juan Pablo II

2019 - 2021

CFGM Microcomputer Systems and Networks

Enrique Tierno Galván

CERTIFICATIONS

2023 - Present

CS50'S Introduction To Artificial Intelligence With Python - Harvard

HarvardX

2023 - Present

Fundamentals Of TinyML - Harvard

HarvardX

2022 - 2023

Game Development With Unity 3D

CES Juan Pablo II

2021 - 2022

Javascript

CES Juan Pablo II

SKILLS

Odoo CRM

UiPath

HTML, CSS, JS y Angular

Python

SQL